With another man?
Seriously?
Is it anyone I know?
No.
He worked for a club
specializing in women's needs.
I happened to bump into him the other day.
A club?
I didn't realize the experience
meant so much to you.
I also questioned myself.
Was sex really so important to me?
But...
I now know I'm a 31 year old woman
who can have proper wants.
Sorry.
That's not a revelation
to be proud of, is it?
I know you treated me well.
I'm so sorry I've hurt you.
[Divorce Forms]
I see. So you told Ouji everything.
Yeah.
Actually, same here.
Huh?
I'll be getting a divorce.
What?
I told my husband everything.
L-Like, "everything"?
Yup. We're discussing the arrangements
as we speak.
What will happen to Chizuka?
We'll be fighting over her custody.
But I'll be paying him
a settlement fee regardless.
I see.
Everyone's making serious confessions, huh?
You started it, Akina.
Yeah.
Huh?
Watching your honorable confession
lit a fire in my heart.
Honorable...
That's one way to put it.
My confession was far from honorable.
I saw how Ouji treasured our relationship,
and knew I couldn't keep secrets anymore.
[Finale]
[Saint Love Survivors]
[What lies after a "happy end"?]
A divorce.
Excuse us.
Kazahaya is ready for you.
Good morning.
I'll be your makeup artist for today.
Fuyumi.
Is it true you got divorced?
We're still fighting over it.
I'm so sorry.
I...
I logically knew it was wrong.
But couldn't talk myself out of it.
And now, I've messed up your family.
Shota, I already had issues with my husband.
Meeting you just gave me the resolve
to file a divorce.
I'm sorry to make you feel responsible.
But, I...
No crying before an important shoot.
Raise your head.
You're an actor, right?
Use that to your advantage.
I had sex with another man.
Why?
Haru!
That's NTR, right?
Huh?
"Netorare".
When you get excited seeing your girl
get it on with another guy.
The hell? Is that a kink?
Can be. It helps reignite some couples, too.
Maybe your friend's in a similar boat?
Well... Who knows.
But in the case of NTR,
the guy isn't looking at their partner
until she's taken, right?
He's disrespecting his girl.
There you are.
Keiko. You here for a shoot?
Yeah. The livestream just ended.
I was looking everywhere for you.
Maybe I was disrespecting her.
Huh?
I thought being with her would be easy.
She was cute.
She wouldn't make romance a pain.
I thought she would always love me.
The cool guy she's come to know.
I'm so lame.
And for our lame narcissist, I have a gift.
Hey, that's that popular novel.
Does Ouji even read?
I'm not interested in books, or fads.
Just read it.
I can't believe I'm pulling an assist.
But we'll call it even here.
What does that... Hey!
[Saint Love Survivors]
This is...
I made a prayer to God.
I didn't care what role I played in his life.
I simply wanted to be a part of it.
But that is most likely where our marriage...
"Went wrong".
[Ouji]
[Haru, I read your book]
[I want to see you]
The book... Like, my book?
H-How did he find out?
[I want to see you]
He's going to ask for a divorce.
[This weekend, Izu. How about it?]
Huh? Izu?
[Izu-Kogen Station]
I came here with the guys once.
Huh?
It's a bit cliche, but it's a nice place.
But... Why Izu?
I wanted to visit a hot spring, remember?
I do, but...
Wait, we're staying overnight?
Yeah.
Oh, don't worry. The inn has most amenities.
That's not why I'm confused.
Aren't we... getting a divorce?
- I wonder.
- Huh?
Come on, let's go.
There, I got a big one.
Nice.
Which one next...
Your crepe, sir.
[Inatori Akao Hotel]
I'm glad you're looking better.
Should we visit the inner garden?
Huh?
It sure gets chilly at night.
Want an extra layer?
Why?
Huh?
I know you're mad.
I know you're in disbelief.
- Huh?
- Don't avoid the subject.
You read the book, didn't you?
I did.
- Then why...
- At first, I was stunned.
You didn't even tell me you were an author.
Sure, you didn't give exact names,
but did you really need to detail everything?
Sorry.
One particular passage
shook me more than anything.
"That is most likely
where our marriage went wrong".
You said every decision you made, was wrong.
No, well...
That's a "me" problem.
Entertaining book, though.
Huh?
Your book.
Maybe that's not much,
coming from a guy who doesn't read.
But at some point,
I stopped caring about the whodunits,
and let myself get absorbed in the story.
It's like I joined the protagonist
on her adventure.
I learned you're an amazing individual, Haru.
Guess what I learned on my second read?
This guy is objectively the worst.
He's an idiot.
No, that's not...
I'm an idiot, too.
I'm an idiot,
but even I can tell.
This book's a love letter.
I can't believe you had so much to say.
You still love me, don't you?
What the heck?
You assume I "still love you"?
Isn't that obvious?
Of course I still love you.
I love your face.
I love your voice, mannerisms, tobacco scent,
bony hands, and the way you wear your boots.
But...
What I truly,
really love about you...
Is that you don't doubt my love for you.
Your honestly dense kindness
has accepted me, time and time again.
Despite how pathetic a person
I actually am.
No, I...
I haven't treated you well at all.
You're an idiot.
You're happy I don't question your love?
I really am a narcissist.
Well, that's...
How can you love me, when I'm so lame?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I made you think you were pathetic.
I'm sorry I made you cry.
Maybe our marriage did go wrong.
But...
We can still right our wrongs, right?
This trip is our official honeymoon.
What the... is this another one of my dreams?
Huh? No. This is real.
What?
You okay?
What about you? Are you okay?
I actually really want to do it.
With you, specifically.
Huh?
Actually, the other night I, uh...
had a reaction for once.
Wanna know why?
You had a dream, about me?
Apparently it happens.
It's called NTR, or something.
Perv.
But I've felt dreamy
seeing you do it out back
with a complete stranger, too.
What? When did that happen?
I guess we're a pair of perverts, huh?
You can say that again.
I can get it in part way.
Damn it, this is so frustrating.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
I felt really good.
But I have to show up Mr. Delivery Guy.
Aw...
Here, I have an idea.
Let me put in some effort.
No, I...
I'll put in my effort, too.
Wait, morning already?
Wow...
The sun's already coming up.
It's 5AM in the morning.
Which means I lasted 6 hours.
At least I outdid him on time.
That's amazing.
If we don't go all the way,
we can mess around forever.
Haru.
I love you.
Marry me?
Too bad. We already are, dummy.
[One year later]
Fuyumi.
Congratulations on the divorce!
I can't believe it ended, just like that.
It helped that he found
another partner for himself.
An assistant 15 years his junior, right?
What a shocker.
How's your love life going, Akina?
Actually...
I've begun seeing someone, sort of.
That's news to me.
- Who is it?
- He's a normal guy.
A coworker who confessed to me.
Nothing bad with normal, I guess.
He looks... kind.
You're allowed to say he looks bland.
We did finally have sex, though.
Also normal, by the way.
Your standards are just way too high.
You can't compare him to a professional.
Aw, but I gave him the time to be pent up.
We're sort of all like survivors.
Survivors?
Survivors of love.
We each had our trials and tribulations,
but we all fought through it, together.
A survivor...
That is what we are, yeah.
How is your love life going, Haru?
Morning.
[Saint Love Survivors]